字幕by: Hongjiang399
微信：Hongjiang399
您好！我是David Gassner.
Hi! My name is David Gassner.
欢迎来到《Java语言基本培训》
And I'd like to welcome you to Java Essential Training.
如果你想要开发用于Java企业服务器或者网页浏览器上
If you want to build native Android apps, dynamic web applications for use on a
的动态网页应用或者本地安卓应用等
Java Enterprise Edition Server or applets that are delivered through a web
那么您需要学习Java语言
browser, you need to know Java.
在本课程里，我将教您怎么在Windows或者Mac OS X上
In this course I'll show you how to download and install the Java Development
下载和安装Java开发工具(简称JDK)
Kit on Windows and Mac OS X and how to get started with Eclipse, the free
以及教您使用免费的跨平台Java集成开发环境--Eclipse软件
cross-platform IDE for Java developers from the Eclipse Foundation.
我将介绍编程语言的基本概念
I'll introduce you to the basics of the programming language including its data
包括数据类型、关键字，以及最好的实践例子
types, keywords and best practices.
Java是一门面向对象的语言，因此我也将介绍
Since Java is a peer object-oriented language I'll describe how it implements
诸如封装、继承以及多态等概念
concepts like encapsulation, inheritance, and polymorphism.
本课程的目的是让您可以开始利用Java语言
The goal of this course is to get you started with Java so you can go on to
开发手机、桌面、网页及其他类型的应用。
build mobile, desktop, Web or other types of applications.
让我们开始课程的学习吧
So let's get started learning Java.
字幕GitHub: https://github.com/Hongjiang399/JavaEssentialTrainingSRT.git